SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in prettify.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in sorter.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in cart.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in lazy-loader.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in order-ui.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in payment-ui.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in performance-dashboard.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in utils.js
SECURITY: document.write usage in QualityAnalyzer.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in AuthUI.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in function-name.test.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in utils.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in html.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in no-eval.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in no-implied-eval.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in index.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in referencer.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in scope-manager.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in scope.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in index.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in sorter.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in prettify.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in bundle.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in api.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in Window.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in xml.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in xpath.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedString.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in utils.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in Document-impl.js
SECURITY: document.write usage in Document-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in HTMLScriptElement-impl.js
SECURITY: document.write usage in HTMLScriptElement-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedString-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in navigation.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in utils.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in api.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in Window.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in xml.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in xpath.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedPreserveAspectRatio.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedRect.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedString.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in utils.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in Document-impl.js
SECURITY: document.write usage in Document-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in HTMLScriptElement-impl.js
SECURITY: document.write usage in HTMLScriptElement-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedPreserveAspectRatio-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedRect-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in SVGAnimatedString-impl.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in navigation.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in browser-source-map-support.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in source-map-support.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in index.js
SECURITY: eval() usage in utils.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in cart.test.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in error-manager.test.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in eventDelegator.test.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in performance.test.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in unit-tests.js
SECURITY: innerHTML assignment in utils.test.js
